<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-11-29T02:29:52+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Darkly Dark</title><subtitle>Simple and yet beautiful design of online shop</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Intel Core i7-9700K Coffee Lake-R, 3.60GHz, Socket 1151, box</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/intel-core-i7-9700k-coffee-lake-r-3-60ghz-socket-1151-box.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Intel Core i7-9700K Coffee Lake-R, 3.60GHz, Socket 1151, box" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/intel-core-i7-9700k-coffee-lake-r-3-60ghz-socket-1151-box</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/intel-core-i7-9700k-coffee-lake-r-3-60ghz-socket-1151-box.html">&lt;section class=&quot;shop-item-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Intel Core i7-9700K Coffee Lake-R, 3.60GHz, Socket 1151, box&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/shop/Intel Core i7-9700K.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
   
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">Intel Core i7-9700K Coffee Lake-R, 3.60GHz, Socket 1151, box</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/shop/Intel%20Core%20i7-9700K.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">AMD Ryzen 2700X, 4.35GHz, 20MB, Socket AM4, Wraith Prism cooler</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/amd-ryzen-2700x-4-35ghz-20mb-socket-am4-wraith-prism-cooler.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AMD Ryzen 2700X, 4.35GHz, 20MB, Socket AM4, Wraith Prism cooler" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/amd-ryzen-2700x-4-35ghz-20mb-socket-am4-wraith-prism-cooler</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/amd-ryzen-2700x-4-35ghz-20mb-socket-am4-wraith-prism-cooler.html">&lt;section class=&quot;shop-item-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;AMD Ryzen 2700X, 4.35GHz, 20MB, Socket AM4, Wraith Prism cooler&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/shop/AMD Ryzen 2700X.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
   
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">AMD Ryzen 2700X, 4.35GHz, 20MB, Socket AM4, Wraith Prism cooler</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/shop/AMD%20Ryzen%202700X.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">AMD Ryzen 5 2600X, 4.25GHz, 19MB, Socket AM4, Wraith Spire cooler</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/amd-ryzen-5-2600x-4-25ghz-19mb-socket-am4-wraith-spire-cooler.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AMD Ryzen 5 2600X, 4.25GHz, 19MB, Socket AM4, Wraith Spire cooler" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/amd-ryzen-5-2600x-4-25ghz-19mb-socket-am4-wraith-spire-cooler</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/amd-ryzen-5-2600x-4-25ghz-19mb-socket-am4-wraith-spire-cooler.html">&lt;section class=&quot;shop-item-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;AMD Ryzen 5 2600X, 4.25GHz, 19MB, Socket AM4, Wraith Spire cooler&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/shop/AMD-Ryzen-5-2600X.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
   
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">AMD Ryzen 5 2600X, 4.25GHz, 19MB, Socket AM4, Wraith Spire cooler</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/shop/AMD-Ryzen-5-2600X.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Intel® Core™ i5-6600K, 3.5GHz, Skylake-S, 6MB, Socket 1151, Box</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/intelr-coretm-i5-6600k-3-5ghz-skylake-s-6mb-socket-1151-box.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Intel® Core™ i5-6600K, 3.5GHz, Skylake-S, 6MB, Socket 1151, Box" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/intelr-coretm-i5-6600k-3-5ghz-skylake-s-6mb-socket-1151-box</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/intelr-coretm-i5-6600k-3-5ghz-skylake-s-6mb-socket-1151-box.html">&lt;section class=&quot;shop-item-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Intel® Core™ i5-6600K, 3.5GHz, Skylake-S, 6MB, Socket 1151, Box&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/shop/Intel Core i5-6600K.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
   
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">Intel® Core™ i5-6600K, 3.5GHz, Skylake-S, 6MB, Socket 1151, Box</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/shop/Intel%20Core%20i5-6600K.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Intel Core i9-9900K Coffee Lake-R, 3.60GHz, Socket 1151, box</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/intel-core-i9-9900k-coffee-lake-r-3-60ghz-socket-1151-box.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Intel Core i9-9900K Coffee Lake-R, 3.60GHz, Socket 1151, box" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/intel-core-i9-9900k-coffee-lake-r-3-60ghz-socket-1151-box</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/shop/items/2018/11/26/intel-core-i9-9900k-coffee-lake-r-3-60ghz-socket-1151-box.html">&lt;section class=&quot;shop-item-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Intel Core i9-9900K Coffee Lake-R, 3.60GHz, Socket 1151, box&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/shop/Intel Core i9-9900K.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
   
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">Intel Core i9-9900K Coffee Lake-R, 3.60GHz, Socket 1151, box</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/shop/Intel%20Core%20i9-9900K.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">No, The NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 Ti Has Not Been Delisted</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/no-nvidia-geforce-rtx-2080-ti-has-not-been-delisted.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="No, The NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 Ti Has Not Been Delisted" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/no-nvidia-geforce-rtx-2080-ti-has-not-been-delisted</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/no-nvidia-geforce-rtx-2080-ti-has-not-been-delisted.html">&lt;section class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;No, The NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 Ti Has Not Been Delisted&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/NVIDIA-GeForce-RTX-2080-Ti-Delisted-Feature-740x370.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;On a slow news day, an NVIDIA high-end GPU being out of stock might be something worth covering, but it takes an
        especially slow-news-day to take an out of stock card, speculate it has been delisted and then contrive a story
        about mass recalls. Contrary to reports you might see floating around, the NVIDIA RTX 2080 Ti has not in fact
        been delisted and is just out of stock. You can tell by simply heading over to Geforce.com and seeing that the
        product page is still there and it appears to be undergoing its usual stock refresh cycles.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;h3&gt;Scandalous scoop: NVIDIA’s RTX 2080 Ti graphics card goes out of stock&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Some media houses have published the out-of-stock status of the RTX 2080 Ti as proof of an impending mass recall
        (to be clear, there is none) and even quoted a forum post which conceded that some initial batches had
        problematic dies – which of course has nothing to do with the OOS status at all and is simply the result of the
        complex nature of the Turing die and how the fabrication process works.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;While I love a good scoop as much as any other tech-head (probably more considering I am the senior editor over
        here¯\_(ツ)_/¯ ), the only sensational scoop I could find in this story is the RTX 2080 Ti being out of stock.
        Ironically, this is actually a good indicator for the card because it means the stock is evaporating faster
        than the company can restock it seamlessly. You can also go out and buy the RTX 2080 Ti from any retailer right
        now – including but not limited to Amazon, Newegg and the like – so there clearly isn’t any recall happening.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Still don’t believe me? I reached out to NVIDIA directly and they practically laughed at this one. They
        confirmed that the card is just out of stock and is undergoing a scheduled restock and will be available for
        purchase before long:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;The eTeknix story is incorrect.

        2080 Ti Founders Edition is available on GeForce.com as usual.

        There seems to be confusion regarding the store link on nvidia.com which defaults to listing products that are
        currently in stock only. If a product does not show up there, that merely means the item is out of stock at the
        time you conducted a search. It does not mean a product has been delisted. Geforce.com is always your best
        choice for all things gaming related.

        &lt;div class=&quot;author&quot;&gt;NVIDIA spokesperson to Darkly Dark&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;If I didn’t know any better, I would think this was a hit-story concocted by shorts of NVIDIA stock wanting to
        make a quick buck and to take advantage of the prevailing sentiment since the quarterly earnings. Shorts have
        already rejoiced and this is the ideal time to take advantage of the presence of bears to bring the stock down
        a further few notches.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;The RTX 2080 Ti is a very complex die – I would even go as far as to call it one of the most complex dies ever
        made for gaming simply because it houses a triumvirate of processor classes inside. It’s hard and expensive to
        fab, and yield bugs are expected when dealing with something like this. But none of that actually translates
        even remotely to anything resembling a mass recall. That is just another example of baseless hysteria for the
        masses and should be avoided for the sake of a healthy rumor mill that we all know and love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">No, The NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 Ti Has Not Been Delisted On a slow news day, an NVIDIA high-end GPU being out of stock might be something worth covering, but it takes an especially slow-news-day to take an out of stock card, speculate it has been delisted and then contrive a story about mass recalls. Contrary to reports you might see floating around, the NVIDIA RTX 2080 Ti has not in fact been delisted and is just out of stock. You can tell by simply heading over to Geforce.com and seeing that the product page is still there and it appears to be undergoing its usual stock refresh cycles.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/NVIDIA-GeForce-RTX-2080-Ti-Delisted-Feature-740x370.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">ADATA Launches The Ultimate SU630 3D QLC NAND SSD</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/adata-launches-the-ultimate-su630-3d-qlc-nand-ssd.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ADATA Launches The Ultimate SU630 3D QLC NAND SSD" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/adata-launches-the-ultimate-su630-3d-qlc-nand-ssd</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/adata-launches-the-ultimate-su630-3d-qlc-nand-ssd.html">&lt;section class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;ADATA Launches The Ultimate SU630 3D QLC NAND SSD&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/ADATA-SU630-2-740x502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;ADATA Technology, a leading manufacturer of high-performance DRAM modules, and mobile accessories today launched
        the ADATA Ultimate SU630 2.5″ SATA 6Gb/s SSD, which signals its expansion into 3D QLC NAND Flash storage. With
        next-generation QLC (Quad-Level Cell) 3D NAND Flash, which ADATA is one of the first to hit the market with, is
        aimed to replace HDDs for an even lower price per gig. This still should have a bit of a trade off with QLC
        having less endurance than current TLC (Triple Level Cell) 3D NAND.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;ADATA Launches Their First QLC SSD SU630&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Delivering excellent performance without the less than great value typically associated with SSDs, the SU630
        gives HDDs a run for their money. It comes in 240GB, 480GB, and 960GB capacities and sports 3D QLC NAND Flash
        to deliver improved reliability, longevity, and performance over its TLC counterparts. Reinforced by
        performance-boosting SLC Caching, the SU630 reaches speeds of 520 MB/s read, and 450 MB/s write for smooth and
        fast boot, file transfers, and downloads. What’s more, the SSD also features characteristics that work to keep
        data safe, including a shock rating of 1500G/0.5ms and resilience to temperature changes (0°C ~ 70°C), while
        also being more energy-efficient and quieter than HDDs.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/ADATA-SU630-1-740x564.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;With support for LDPC (Low-Density Parity-Check) ECC (error correcting code) technology, the SU630 can detect
        and fix errors to ensure data integrity and thus enjoy an extended lifespan. On top of that, with the purchase
        of the SU630, users qualify to download ADATA’s SSD Toolbox and Migration Utility free of charge. SSD Toolbox
        allows users to monitor and manage the SU630, with drive status, wear level, and lifespan information. The
        Migration Utility is especially helpful for users making the switch from HDD to SSD, as it allows for simple
        and straightforward backup and migration of data, including the operating system.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;That being said ADATA did note on their website a Warranty of only 2 years, a year shorter than the industry
        standard 3 years. It remains to be seen how long of an endurance future QLC NAND SSDs have and this is not a
        knock on ADATA specifically.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Pricing And Availability&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Pricing has not been announced though it should be hitting store shelves in the coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">ADATA Launches The Ultimate SU630 3D QLC NAND SSD ADATA Technology, a leading manufacturer of high-performance DRAM modules, and mobile accessories today launched the ADATA Ultimate SU630 2.5″ SATA 6Gb/s SSD, which signals its expansion into 3D QLC NAND Flash storage. With next-generation QLC (Quad-Level Cell) 3D NAND Flash, which ADATA is one of the first to hit the market with, is aimed to replace HDDs for an even lower price per gig. This still should have a bit of a trade off with QLC having less endurance than current TLC (Triple Level Cell) 3D NAND. ADATA Launches Their First QLC SSD SU630 Delivering excellent performance without the less than great value typically associated with SSDs, the SU630 gives HDDs a run for their money. It comes in 240GB, 480GB, and 960GB capacities and sports 3D QLC NAND Flash to deliver improved reliability, longevity, and performance over its TLC counterparts. Reinforced by performance-boosting SLC Caching, the SU630 reaches speeds of 520 MB/s read, and 450 MB/s write for smooth and fast boot, file transfers, and downloads. What’s more, the SSD also features characteristics that work to keep data safe, including a shock rating of 1500G/0.5ms and resilience to temperature changes (0°C ~ 70°C), while also being more energy-efficient and quieter than HDDs. With support for LDPC (Low-Density Parity-Check) ECC (error correcting code) technology, the SU630 can detect and fix errors to ensure data integrity and thus enjoy an extended lifespan. On top of that, with the purchase of the SU630, users qualify to download ADATA’s SSD Toolbox and Migration Utility free of charge. SSD Toolbox allows users to monitor and manage the SU630, with drive status, wear level, and lifespan information. The Migration Utility is especially helpful for users making the switch from HDD to SSD, as it allows for simple and straightforward backup and migration of data, including the operating system. That being said ADATA did note on their website a Warranty of only 2 years, a year shorter than the industry standard 3 years. It remains to be seen how long of an endurance future QLC NAND SSDs have and this is not a knock on ADATA specifically. Pricing And Availability Pricing has not been announced though it should be hitting store shelves in the coming weeks.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/ADATA-SU630-2-740x502.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">ASUS Launches New ROG Strix Radeon RX 590 Graphics Card</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/asus-launches-new-rog-strix-radeon-rx-590-graphics-card.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ASUS Launches New ROG Strix Radeon RX 590 Graphics Card" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/asus-launches-new-rog-strix-radeon-rx-590-graphics-card</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/asus-launches-new-rog-strix-radeon-rx-590-graphics-card.html">&lt;section class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;ASUS Launches New ROG Strix Radeon RX 590 Graphics Card&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/ASUS-ROG-STRIX-RX-590-1-740x607.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;For those waiting to pack their ASUS Themed build with an Strix ROG RX 590, wait no longer as earlier this week
        Asus has announced their ROG Strix Radeon RX 590, an all-new graphics card powered by AMD’s latest Radeon RX
        590 GPU and engineered with the cooling, reliability, performance, and customizable lighting you would expect
        out of an ROG Product.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;ASUS Launches New ROG STRIX Radeon RX 590&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;ASUS touts its superior cooling potential as well as efficient fans that keep noise low and airflow high, up to
        105% more static pressure compared to axial designs. They also note it uses their “MaxContact” technology in
        which the heat spreaders are precision machined on the surface which they say can make up to twice as much
        contact with the GPU allowing a more efficient thermal transfer. This could be the difference between a few
        Celsius here or there. The aforementioned fans also remain silent until the GPU temperature hits above 55
        Celcius.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The fan internals are also sealed to IP5X standards so that they will keep running, even in dusty environments.
        Dust-resistant fans aren’t the only technology that makes ROG Strix graphics cards well-known for reliability;
        Auto-extreme technology is an automated manufacturing process that sets new standards in the industry by
        allowing all soldering to be completed in a single pass.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This reduces thermal strain on components and avoids the use of harsh cleaning chemicals, resulting in less
        environmental impact, for those consumers worried about how “green” the hardware they use. It also lowers
        manufacturing power consumption and a more reliable product overall.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/ASUS-ROG-STRIX-RX-590-4-740x381.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Finally, it uses a seven-phase voltage regulator with what Asus calls high-end premium chokes and solid polymer
        capacitors, and high current power stages. All of this should allow high end overclocking and hopefully push
        past 1600MHz reliably. Lastly, the card is equipped with ASUS Aura Sync RGB Lighting on the shroud and
        backplate. We have spoken at length in the past about how many products easily sync into ASUS’s Aura Sync
        software and it’s quality.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Pricing And Availability&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Pricing is expected to be just shy of $300, though ASUS has not given us official word. Also it is likely that
        this card will include the 3 game bundle AMD is including with all of their 590s that pack Devil May Cry 5, The
        Division 2 and Resident Evil 2 (The upcoming Remake). This should add a bit to the total value of the card
        overall.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We do expect the release to be imminent and will update the article when further info arises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">ASUS Launches New ROG Strix Radeon RX 590 Graphics Card For those waiting to pack their ASUS Themed build with an Strix ROG RX 590, wait no longer as earlier this week Asus has announced their ROG Strix Radeon RX 590, an all-new graphics card powered by AMD’s latest Radeon RX 590 GPU and engineered with the cooling, reliability, performance, and customizable lighting you would expect out of an ROG Product. ASUS Launches New ROG STRIX Radeon RX 590 ASUS touts its superior cooling potential as well as efficient fans that keep noise low and airflow high, up to 105% more static pressure compared to axial designs. They also note it uses their “MaxContact” technology in which the heat spreaders are precision machined on the surface which they say can make up to twice as much contact with the GPU allowing a more efficient thermal transfer. This could be the difference between a few Celsius here or there. The aforementioned fans also remain silent until the GPU temperature hits above 55 Celcius. The fan internals are also sealed to IP5X standards so that they will keep running, even in dusty environments. Dust-resistant fans aren’t the only technology that makes ROG Strix graphics cards well-known for reliability; Auto-extreme technology is an automated manufacturing process that sets new standards in the industry by allowing all soldering to be completed in a single pass. This reduces thermal strain on components and avoids the use of harsh cleaning chemicals, resulting in less environmental impact, for those consumers worried about how “green” the hardware they use. It also lowers manufacturing power consumption and a more reliable product overall. Finally, it uses a seven-phase voltage regulator with what Asus calls high-end premium chokes and solid polymer capacitors, and high current power stages. All of this should allow high end overclocking and hopefully push past 1600MHz reliably. Lastly, the card is equipped with ASUS Aura Sync RGB Lighting on the shroud and backplate. We have spoken at length in the past about how many products easily sync into ASUS’s Aura Sync software and it’s quality. Pricing And Availability Pricing is expected to be just shy of $300, though ASUS has not given us official word. Also it is likely that this card will include the 3 game bundle AMD is including with all of their 590s that pack Devil May Cry 5, The Division 2 and Resident Evil 2 (The upcoming Remake). This should add a bit to the total value of the card overall. We do expect the release to be imminent and will update the article when further info arises.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/ASUS-ROG-STRIX-RX-590-1-740x607.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Antec Launches New Prizm Addressable RGB Fans</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/antec-launches-new-prizm-addressable-rgb-fans.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Antec Launches New Prizm Addressable RGB Fans" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/antec-launches-new-prizm-addressable-rgb-fans</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/antec-launches-new-prizm-addressable-rgb-fans.html">&lt;section class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;Antec Launches New Prizm Addressable RGB Fans&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/Antec-Prizm-Fans-4-740x347.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Antec Inc., a leading provider of high-performance computer components and accessories for the gaming, PC
        upgrade and Do-It-Yourself market, presents their new ARGB case fans, the PRIZM ARGB series. Taking style,
        performance and silence to the next level, Prizm ARGB is available in 120/140 mm, and is surrounded by a ring
        of addressable RGB LEDs and high-performance fan blades including the addressable RGB LED controller.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Antec Jumps into the Addressable RGB Fray with Prizm Case Fans&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Illuminating the PC inside and out, the fans are characterized by dual-sided RGB LED lighting ring with 18
        independently-controllable LEDs. The Prizm ARGB fans are using the addressable RGB standard and are certified
        compatible with Asus Aura, Gigabyte RGB Fusion, ASRock RGB and MSI RGB. The PWM fans optimize heat dissipation
        and hydraulic bearing which ensures ultra-quiet operation. Both models feature 4-pin PWM input and around 32
        dBA maximum noise output. The 120 mm model spins up to 2.000 RPM, pushing up to 45.03 CFM of air, while the 140
        mm model spins up to 1.700 RPM, with up to 65.03 CFM air flow. Both models are backed by a warranty period of
        two years.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/Antec-Prizm-Fans-2-740x560.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Prizm ARGB fans offer a perfect harmony between excellent cooling performance and unique style as well as
        noise-reducing technology and easy installation experience.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;All in all, these seem priced decently but nothing really groundbreaking. That being said fans generally aren’t
        a groundbreaking product. The RPM numbers are pretty good, though I am interested to know what the sound
        profile for these would sound like&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Pricing And Availability&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Set of 3 Prizm 120 ARGB 3+2+C (3in1 pack &amp; fan controller &amp; ARGB LED Strips) 87€ $79.95 USD&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Set of 5 Prizm 120 ARGB 5+C (5 in 1 pack with fan controller): 95€ $95 USD&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Set of 2 Prizm 140 ARGB 2+C (2 in 1 pack with fan controller): 54€ $65 USD&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 Prizm 140 ARGB (Single pack):19€ $25 USD&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 Prizm 120 ARGB (Single pack): $19 USD&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">Antec Launches New Prizm Addressable RGB Fans Antec Inc., a leading provider of high-performance computer components and accessories for the gaming, PC upgrade and Do-It-Yourself market, presents their new ARGB case fans, the PRIZM ARGB series. Taking style, performance and silence to the next level, Prizm ARGB is available in 120/140 mm, and is surrounded by a ring of addressable RGB LEDs and high-performance fan blades including the addressable RGB LED controller. Antec Jumps into the Addressable RGB Fray with Prizm Case Fans Illuminating the PC inside and out, the fans are characterized by dual-sided RGB LED lighting ring with 18 independently-controllable LEDs. The Prizm ARGB fans are using the addressable RGB standard and are certified compatible with Asus Aura, Gigabyte RGB Fusion, ASRock RGB and MSI RGB. The PWM fans optimize heat dissipation and hydraulic bearing which ensures ultra-quiet operation. Both models feature 4-pin PWM input and around 32 dBA maximum noise output. The 120 mm model spins up to 2.000 RPM, pushing up to 45.03 CFM of air, while the 140 mm model spins up to 1.700 RPM, with up to 65.03 CFM air flow. Both models are backed by a warranty period of two years. The Prizm ARGB fans offer a perfect harmony between excellent cooling performance and unique style as well as noise-reducing technology and easy installation experience. All in all, these seem priced decently but nothing really groundbreaking. That being said fans generally aren’t a groundbreaking product. The RPM numbers are pretty good, though I am interested to know what the sound profile for these would sound like Pricing And Availability Set of 3 Prizm 120 ARGB 3+2+C (3in1 pack &amp; fan controller &amp; ARGB LED Strips) 87€ $79.95 USD Set of 5 Prizm 120 ARGB 5+C (5 in 1 pack with fan controller): 95€ $95 USD Set of 2 Prizm 140 ARGB 2+C (2 in 1 pack with fan controller): 54€ $65 USD 1 Prizm 140 ARGB (Single pack):19€ $25 USD 1 Prizm 120 ARGB (Single pack): $19 USD</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/Antec-Prizm-Fans-4-740x347.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">AMD’s Zen 2 7nm CPU Core to Feature Double the L3 Cache Size</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/amds-next-gen-zen-2-7nm-cpu-core-to-feature-double-l3-cache-size.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AMD’s Zen 2 7nm CPU Core to Feature Double the L3 Cache Size" /><published>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T13:14:21+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/amds-next-gen-zen-2-7nm-cpu-core-to-feature-double-l3-cache-size</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Darkly-Dark/blog/news/2018/11/26/amds-next-gen-zen-2-7nm-cpu-core-to-feature-double-l3-cache-size.html">&lt;section class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h2&gt;AMD’s Zen 2 7nm CPU Core to Feature Double the L3 Cache Size&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/AMD-X499-HEDT-Platform-Ryzen-Threadripper-CPUs-740x370.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;AMD’s next generation “Zen 2” core, which is slated for release some time next year, was a largely a mystery up
        until earlier in the month when the company took the covers off what its CPU engineering team has been cooking
        in its labs and it’s quite the tasty recipe!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Zen 2, despite its name, is actually going to power the company’s 3rd generation lineup of Ryzen processors. We
        have already seen the company’s 2nd generation product in the form of the 2000 series Ryzen lineup. Which
        brought us some algorithmic power and frequency fine tuning in addition to an improved FinFET process. With
        that being said, AMD does not consider 2nd generation Ryzen a redesign but rather a refinement of first
        generation Zen, which is expected to hold the line until 7nm is ready for prime-time next year.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/2018-11-06_22-50-43-1030x476.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We have already covered the bulk of new architectural improvements that AMD is bringing to the table with its
        next generation Zen 2 core built on TSMC’s 7nm process tech. Which you can find in the link above, however
        here’s a refresher of some of the key enhancements :&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Improved Execution Pipeline&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Doubled Floating Point (256-bit) and Load/Store (Doubled Bandwidth)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Doubled Core Density&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Half the Energy Per Operation&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Improved Branch Prediction&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Better Instruction Pre-Fetching&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Re-Optimized Instruction Cache&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Larger Op Cache&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Increased Dispatch / Retire Bandwidth&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Maintaining High Throughput for All Modes&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;And now, thanks to a leak on the SiSoft SANDRA database via TPU, we can also add double the L3 cache to that
        list. An entry for an upcoming ROME processor featuring the company’s Zen 2 core has popped up and it revealed
        that the 64 core chip actually features a whopping 256MB of L3 cache. That’s 16 MB per CCX, double that of the
        previous generation.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&quot;/Darkly-Dark/images/blog/YnwEaEEs7ybTXTPj-1030x635.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This indicates that we will likely see AMD debut 8 core mainstream Ryzen 3000 series processors with 32MB of L3
        cache. A larger L3 means that the system would have to fetch data from DDR4 memory less often, which translates
        to faster work completion at less power. Undoubtedly contributing to the IPC and power efficiency gains that
        Zen 2 brings to the table compared to the original Zen design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name>Maverick</name></author><summary type="html">AMD’s Zen 2 7nm CPU Core to Feature Double the L3 Cache Size AMD’s next generation “Zen 2” core, which is slated for release some time next year, was a largely a mystery up until earlier in the month when the company took the covers off what its CPU engineering team has been cooking in its labs and it’s quite the tasty recipe! Zen 2, despite its name, is actually going to power the company’s 3rd generation lineup of Ryzen processors. We have already seen the company’s 2nd generation product in the form of the 2000 series Ryzen lineup. Which brought us some algorithmic power and frequency fine tuning in addition to an improved FinFET process. With that being said, AMD does not consider 2nd generation Ryzen a redesign but rather a refinement of first generation Zen, which is expected to hold the line until 7nm is ready for prime-time next year. We have already covered the bulk of new architectural improvements that AMD is bringing to the table with its next generation Zen 2 core built on TSMC’s 7nm process tech. Which you can find in the link above, however here’s a refresher of some of the key enhancements : Improved Execution Pipeline Doubled Floating Point (256-bit) and Load/Store (Doubled Bandwidth) Doubled Core Density Half the Energy Per Operation Improved Branch Prediction Better Instruction Pre-Fetching Re-Optimized Instruction Cache Larger Op Cache Increased Dispatch / Retire Bandwidth Maintaining High Throughput for All Modes</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/blog/AMD-X499-HEDT-Platform-Ryzen-Threadripper-CPUs-740x370.png" /></entry></feed>